Kar do
[music]
Hello hello and welcome to
another video of share market knowledge
today we are going to talk about the
shares of Escorts Limited. If you are
new to my channel then subscribe to the channel as well. Let's
start with the review.
Subscribe to the last video I made,
subscribe to the channel
and
subscribe.
Do subscribe to the channel. I will give you
almost the
charts on this which are not in hatred against others. So
what is the result of this,
I like
this
orange
juice very well but
I did
subscribe to the channel. Do subscribe to
any company. There is
always such a pattern, poison in a new mouth. If you
ask me as much as you want, I
can show you very accurately. This is this chart or
any chart, how to get up on their religion. For example, I can show you this here, for example,
I will show you this here, that is why I
always try,
subscribe, but
if something similar happens in the form of a fall in starting in this manner, not only
this, subscribe to this
channel,
Chapra Npr, from here, 1450 toss, the eighth
festival can be done very comfortably.
Please subscribe a little and
you can
see a fifteen percent increase in your subscriptions. If you are
not feeling like subscribing, then
subscribe for this and if you liked this video
subscribe
show more, then please
like and share it
and I will take it from you in my next video, till then take
care of yourself and all the best.